（古市）ふぅ～。
（ノック）
んっ！？…誰だ？
Who's that?
えっ　嘘？何？
あれは…女の子のシルエット？
No way...
Is that...
...a girl's silhouette?
フッ…フッ…。
ガーン！！
（アランドロン）古市殿　お背中
お流ししましょうか？
Furuichi-dono, shall I wash your back?
いらね～よ～！
No, thanks!
（アランドロン）そうですか。
では　私も失礼して…。
Oh...
Then, if you'll pardon me.
（古市）恥らうなぁあああっ～！！
Don't you dare blush!
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんなことから
赤ん坊を育てることになった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語…ムフッ。
ただし　その赤ん坊は→
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
But this baby is no ordinary baby...
普通の赤ん坊ではなく
魔王の子…古市殿～～っ！！＞
It is a baby...
...Furuichi-dono!
（古市）出てけ～！！
Get out!
The Delinquents have Changed into Swimsuits
（チャイム）
（古市）
…というわけで　いいかげん→
So you see, I can't bear the
big guy's SH any more...
あのオッサンのセクハラに
耐えかねているわけだが…。
Furuichi-dono
（男鹿）セクシーサプリメントか。
セクシャルハラスメントな。
Sexy Herbal Supplements, huh?
Sexual harassment...
ま…い～じゃねぇか。
好かれてんだし。
Well, what's so wrong with being loved?
Plenty!
よかねぇ！！相手は悪魔だぞ！？
He's a demon!
しかも　オッサンだぞ！？
お前が　とっととベル坊を→
And he's a old dude!
Until you hurry up and find
someone to dump Baby Beel off on,
押し付ける相手を見つけないから
いつまでも居座ってんだろ！
he'll be squatting at my place forever!
つーか…石矢魔には
もう強い奴いねぇだろ。
But there aren't any more
strong guys at Ishiyama...
いや。まだ　東邦神姫の
最後の　ひとりが残ってる！
No. There's still the
final member of the TKKH.
東条秀虎！→
Tojo Hidetora!
噂によれば
石矢魔　最強らしい…。→
The rumors claim he's the
strongest in Ishiyama.
スッポン高の３５０人を
たった１人で全滅させたとか…。
Like how he wiped out 350 people
from Suppon High all by himself...
（古市）北海道の最強不良高
毛ガニ高の幹部を→
Or how he beat the leader of the most
powerful JD school in Hokkaido, Kegani High,
２秒で倒したとか…。
in only 2 seconds!
（ベル坊）ダブ～！
Anyway, he's got plenty of legends about him.
とにかく　数々の伝説を持つ男だ！おもしれぇな…。
Interesting.
どんな奴か
見に行ってみっか。
Let's go check this guy out.
だが　バイトばっかしてて滅多に
学校出てこないらしいけどな。
But he's always doing odd-jobs and
hardly ever comes to school, I hear.
バブ～！！
古市　捜して来いや！！
Go find him, Furuichi!
（古市）お～う！！
（夏目）へぇ～　男鹿ちゃん
東条を捜してたんだ。
Oh?
Oga-chan is looking for Tojo?
（夏目）いよいよ　決戦か…。
I guess the last battle is finally here.
（城山）いくら　男鹿でも
東条に勝てるとは思えん。
I don't care how strong Oga is, I don't
think he'll be able to beat Tojo.
（夏目）
どっちにしたって　２人とも
石矢魔統一には興味ないからね。
Either way, neither of them have
any interest in uniting Ishiyama.
It'd be best for the two of
them to crush each other.
（神崎）２人で勝手に…つぶし合ってくれればいんだがな。
（姫川）フッフフ…それ　いいね。
That'd be nice.
（チャイム）
あっ　姫川…。
Himekawa!
よお…男鹿のヤツ
東条　捜してんだって？
Yo...
Oga's searching for Tojo, is he?
（古市）なぜ　それを…。
How do you know?
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
や～　俺　期待してっから…→
男鹿なら　東条を
倒してくれるに違いないって。
I'm sure Oga will beat Tojo for me, no doubt.
Part Timers Wanted
Salary: 830 yen+
Qualifications: 18 and older
Time: 5 hours+ a day
Special Note: Travel Expenses Paid
Looking Especially for Energetic, Cheerful Workers
（姫川）フフッ…
調べておいてやったぜ。
I did some searching.
Beach House Fujitsubo
Ishiyama Beach
これ　今の東条のバイト先。
男鹿に伝えてくれ。
This is where Tojo is working part-time now.
Tell Oga for me.
海の家…！？
A beach house?
Beach house?!
《海の家…！》
Girls in swimsuits!
（古市）《水着のお姉さんたち！》
《いや　そんな事よりも…
ベル坊が行くなら→
No, more importantly... If Baby Beel
comes with him, then Hilda-san will, too!
ヒルダさんも一緒…だとすれば
ヒルダさんの水着が見れる！→
In that case...
...I'll get to see Hilda-san in a swimsuit!
魔界の水着！？
きっと　人間界の水着など→
A Demon World swimsuit...
I'm sure it'll put any swimsuit
in the Human World to shame!
かすんでしまうぐらい
すごい水着に違いない…→
どんな水着だ？…貝殻か？→
What kind of swimsuit?
Seashells?
ヤシの実か？》
Coconuts?
No, no, no...
《いやいやいや…
なんつっても魔界だ！→
It's from the Demon World, so it wouldn't
be a wimpy swimsuit like those!
そんな　やわな水着じゃない！
もっとエロくて　過激で→
It's gotta be a sexier,
extremely dangerous swimsuit!
デンジャラスなヤツに違いない！
グッ…グフッ》
姫川先輩！
ありがとうございます。
お…おう。
Himekawa-senpai, thank you very much!
S-Sure...
（古川）海だ　海だ！
水着だ　水着だ～！！→
The beach, the beach!
Swimsuits, swimsuits!
Hey, Oga! I know where Tojo is!
お～い　男鹿！
東条の居場所が判ったぞ～！
フッフフ…。
（邦枝）あいつら…男鹿に東条を
ぶつけるつもりなの？
Is he planning to get Tojo to beat Oga?
（寧々）うちらには
関係ありませんよ　姐さん→
It has nothing to do with us, Madame.
Tojo or whoever, they can crush
each other all they want.
東条でも何でも　勝手に
ぶつかって勝手に潰し合えばいい。
（千秋）うん。
（邦枝）
《いくら　男鹿辰巳でも
あの東条には勝てない…》
I don't care how strong Oga Tatsumi
is... He can't beat the Tojo I know.
（海鳥の鳴き声）
Unsatisfying...
（東条）虚しい…もっと→
Isn't there anyone that's
a real challenge out there?
手応えのあるヤツは
いねぇのか？
（相沢）派手にやりましたね。
You sure did a real number on them.
And thanks to it, I got fired
from my hard-won beach house job.
（東条）おかげで　せっかくみつけた海の家のバイトがクビだ…。
フフッ…まあ
また　探しましょうや。
Well, we can just search again.
（陣野）ヤキソバおごって
貰おうと思ったのに…。
I had hoped you'd score
me some free yakisoba.
（東条）悪いな…かおる。
つ～かさ　どっかに→
Sorry 'bout that, Kaoru.
Anyway, isn't there someone out
there that's a match for me?
オレとタメはれるような
ヤツは　いねぇのかな？
それなんスけどね…東条さん
ひとり　いきのいいのがいますよ。
Well, about that, Tojo-san...
There's one guy that's promising.
（東条）あっ？
男鹿辰巳。
うちの１年なんスが→
Oga Tatsumi.
He's a first year at our school, but he's
beat Kanzaki, Himekawa, and even Kunieda.
この間　神崎　姫川に続き
邦枝までやっちまった。
（東条）ほう…。
Oh?
海だな…。
ダァ～。
The beach.
（古市）ああ　海だ。
Yes, the beach.
つ～か…ここ　ベル坊のおもらし
捨てに来た海岸じゃね～か？
Wait, isn't this the shore where we
got rid of Baby Beel's "monsoon"?
（古市）そういわれると
なんか泳ぐ気しね～…。
Yeah... Maybe I'll pass on taking a dip.
いやいや…俺たちは何も
泳ぎに来たんわけじゃない。
But anyway, we didn't come for a swim!
東条を捜しに来たんだ！
そして　もう１つ重要なのは…→
We came to look for Tojo!
Plus there's one more important thing...
で…どうなんだ？ヒルダさんは水着を用意してきたのか？
Erm... Did Hilda-san bring a swimsuit?
ん～…ああ。
そういや～　何か→
Oh, yeah... She said she brought some
kind of amazing Demon World swimsuit...
ものすごい魔界の水着
持ってきたつってたな～。
わぁ～！ヒルダさんの…
ものすごい水着！
Hilda-san... amazing swimsuit...
（ヒルダ）
((あまりジロジロ見るでない
照れるであろう…))
Do not stare like that.
It is embarrassing...
夢が　ふくらむね…。
My dreams are ever growing.
So, let us change into a swimsuit.
では　水着に着替えるとするか。
なっ！？
こ…ここで着替えるんですか！？
You're going to change there?
いけないか？
It's unacceptable?
全然ＯＫです！
むしろ　歓迎です！！
It's totally fine!
Rather, it's the perfect place!
ムフッ…ムフフフッ…。
（古市）エヘヘヘ…。
あまりジロジロ見るでない。
照れるであろう。
Do not stare like that.
It is embarrassing.
ダブ～！
…って　お前かよ。
It's you?
ダッ！
Furuichi-dono, if you want to stare...
（アランドロン）古市殿　見るなら私を…。
えっ！？
ウフ～ン…。
カァァ～ン…。
何やってる。行くぞ　古市！
What are you doing?
Let's go, Furuichi.
海の家…ふじつぼ。
Beach house Fujitsubo...
ここか…。
This is it.
（店長）あ～！ちょっとそこ！→
Hey, you!
ダメだよ！
ちゃんと並んで！
You have to get in line!
はっ！？
ダッ！
いや　オレたち…別にヤキソバ
買いに来たわけじゃなくて…。
Uh, we didn't come to buy Yakisoba.
あっ！
君たち　新しいバイト！？→
Wait, are you the new part-timers?
I've been waiting!
待ってたよ～。
こっちこっち…早く早く！
This way!
Hurry up!
（古市）えっ…ちょっと～違う…。
バブ～！
No, that's not it!
≪いくよ～≫
≪おう！≫≪は～い！≫
パパ～　まだぁ～。
Papa... How much longer?
（父親）ああ　もう少しかな…。
Just a little longer...
すぐ　できまちゅからね～→
It'll be weady wight away!
…って　オレたち何やってんだ？
Wait, what are we doing?
ここで　東条が来るの
待ってれば　いいんじゃね？
Why don't we just wait here until Tojo comes?
だって　ほら…
オレたち　東条の顔　知らね～し→
After all, we don't know
what Tojo looks like...
はい。お待たせ！次の方～。
Here, thanks for waiting!
Who's next?
あたし　紅ショウガ
抜いて下さ～い。
あたし　大盛りで！
Hold the ginger on mine, please!
I'd like an extra large!
は～い　かしこまりました～！
Coming right up!
≪きゃあ～かわいい！≫
ん！？
≪赤ちゃんだ～！≫
Ooh, how cute!
It's a baby!
≪かわいい～≫バブ～。
≪こっち向いて≫
バブ～。
いいのか…これで。
Uh, is this gonna be okay?
≪わぁ～　美味しそう≫
≪早く早く！≫
わぁ～…天国だ！
ここはハーレムだぁ～。
I'm in heaven...
I've got a harem!
（姫川）何やってんだ…あいつら→
What is he doing?
せっかく　東条と引き合わせようとしてやってんのに…。
I thought I'd finally gotten
Tojo and him together...
（城山）
どうやら　東条のヤツ…バイト
クビになったみたいですよ。
It seems like Tojo's been fired.
なんだと？
それじゃあ　俺たちは→
What?
Then what did we come here for?
何しに　こんなとこまで
来たんだ…あっ？
（夏目）神崎く～ん！
Kanzaki-kun, they have some amazing yogurti!
すごいヨーグルッチが
あったよ～！→
ほら　イカ風味！
Look, it's squid-flavor!
城山　ちょっと
はい。おまえ　飲んでみろ。
Shiroyama, try a little.
Here.
うむ…ズズーッ…。
ウエッ！
（神崎）ん？…邦枝…。
Kunieda?
《結局
気になって来てしまった…》
I ended up being worried and coming here...
お姉さん　ひとり？
You alone, Miss?
俺たちと遊ばない？
Wanna play with us?
（殴る音）
ぐああ～～っ！
ひええっ～～！
≪ああ～っ…≫
≪うわっ！≫
（店長）いや～　お疲れさん！→
Great work!
いいね～
君たち　大盛況だよ～！
You guys are great!
A big success!
あの～…ところで東条は
いつになったら来るんですか？
Um... When will Tojo be coming?
え？東条君なら
昨日クビにしたけど。
Tojo-kun... He was fired yesterday.
クビ！？
Fired?
お客さんと
ケンカしちゃったからさ～。
He fought with some customers.
ホラ　あれ…。
See that?
あれ曲げたの　東条！？ダブ～！！
Did Tojo bend that?
まあ　お客さんといっても
ガラの悪い奴らだったんだけどね。
Well, I called them customers,
but they were a bunch of thugs.
何？君たち　東条君の友達？
What, are you friends of his?
ほぉ！てめえら　東条の仲間か！？
Oh? You're with Tojo, are ya?
ひいぃ～！また来た～！！
They're back!
ダーブー！！ダ～ッ！
You did a real number on us yesterday.
昨日は派手に
やってくれたそうじゃねぇか。
東条　出せや！
Where're you hidin' Tojo?
それとも　お前が代わりに
落とし前つけるか？ああ～ん？
Bring him, or we beat you in his place!
うるせぇ…。
Shut up.
ひええぇ～！
て　てめえ！
このやろう！！
W-Why you...
おら～～っ！！
（乱闘する音）
結局　空振りに終わっちまったな。
ダブー！！
Well, I guess this was a swing and a miss...
≪おい　あっちに石矢魔の
クイーンが来てるぜ！≫
Hey, Ishiyama's Queen showed up over there!
マジか？ヤバくねぇ？それ。
For real?
That spells trouble!
ヤベぇなんてもんじゃねぇ！
すげえ水着だ！！
Better than trouble, I hear
she's in a dangerous swimsuit!
クイーンが来てる？
それも水着！？
The Queen is here? And in a swimsuit?
おい　男鹿！早くしろ！！行くぞ～！
お　おい　古市…。
Hey Oga, hurry up!
Off we go!
ああ…。
（碇）さすが石矢魔のクイーン。
Indeed, you are Ishiyama's Queen.
みんなが見とれてますよ
美破さん。
Everyone is staring at you, Miwa-san.
確かにヤベ～な…。
ゲー…。
Definitely dangerous, all right.
見なかった事にしよう…。
Let's pretend we didn't see that.
（アランドロン）
何やら皆さん集まって…→
I do believe everyone has arrived...
This could get quite lively.
にぎやかな事になりそうですね。
フン　雑魚に興味はない。
I have no interest in weaklings.
問題は　その東条とかいう奴だ。
The issue is with this Tojo person.
Arm Wrestling
100 Yen a Try
どうやら男鹿の奴も
この海岸に来てるらしいですよ。
It seems that Oga person
has shown up on this beach.
ほお…。
Oh?
面白くなってきたじゃねぇか…。
Things are gonna get fun.
ダブ！ダッダ～！ダーダブ～！！
（ヒューン　ヒューン…）
Starfish shuriken!
（古市）ヒトデ　手裏剣！
ナマコ　クナイ！
Sea cucumber kunai!
やるな　おぬし。
You have skills, sir!
As do you!
うぬこそ！フッ！！
What is this?
なんと！それっ！！
Take that!
なんのなんの…おっとっと…。
ダブ～ッ！ビエエ…。
ビエ～～ッ！！
ぎゃあああ～っ！！
あ　クイーン…。
あ…ああ…。
Queen?
Oga Tatsumi... Looks like you burn easily...
男鹿辰巳…すいぶん焼けたわね。
ひえぇ～！
ったく　なんでだよ…。
Sheesh... Why?
It's the beach! If you're gonna come, you
could show a little more skin than that!
おかしいだろ　クイーン。
海に来て
あの露出のなさはないだろ…。
You over there, young man...
（お姉さん）
ちょっと　そこの坊や。
へっ…？
Yes! Young man here, at your service!
はい！坊やです！！何でしょうか？
This is from Hime-chan.
（お姉さん）これ　姫ちゃんから。
Hime-chan?
（古市）姫ちゃん？って　姫川？→
You mean, Himekawa?
「電気くらげ」…？
Electric jellyfish?
That's where Tojo is.
そこに東条がいるって。
あ…。
ダブ！ダッダッ！アイアイ…。
まあ～上手い上手い！
You're really good at this.
《私　何やってんだろ…》
What am I doing?
Why are you so good at caring for a baby?
なんだよ　お前ずいぶん
赤ん坊の扱いに慣れてんな。
へっ！？いや…そんな事はない！
T-That's not true...
Oga!
（古市）男鹿～！東条の居場所が
分かったぞ！！
I know where Tojo is!
You do?
ホントか？よし　行くぞ　ベル坊！！
All right! Let's go, Baby Beel!
ダーブ…。
どうした　ベル坊？
What's wrong, Baby Beel?
ダブ～！
右！右！右！
You wish to do that next, young Master?
坊っちゃま　今度は
あれが　やりたいのですか？
ダブ。
スイカはあるか？
Do we have a watermelon?
In that case, I...
それでは　私が…
スイカの代わりに。
...will become the melon.
Actually, splitting you
here would be a problem.
いや…ここで
オッサン割るのは　まずいだろ。
Then perhaps I shall split
myself from the start?
では　最初から
割れておきましょうか？
Don't split yourself!
キャー！！
割れるな！
（姫川）あいつら…一体…→
What in the world are they doing?
何やってんだ…。
（神崎）うおお…。
Kanzaki-san... Perhaps we
shouldn't expect much here.
神崎さん…もう
期待しない方がいいんじゃ…。
Store closed
フン…男鹿ってヤロー→
Look at that bastard Oga...
Not bad, I say.
なかなか
やるみてぇじゃねぇか…。
Electric Jellyfish
ああ。東条なら
さっき　あがったよ。
Tojo? He finished up just earlier.
Crap... There's never
gonna be an end to this.
ダメだ…このままじゃ
ラチがあかねぇ！
I know, Oga! Write him a letter of challenge.
そうだ　男鹿。果たし状を書け！→
それを東条に届けるんだ。
おお！
Then deliver it to Tojo.
Letter of Challenge
I'll be waiting in front of the
two rocks tonight at 5 PM.
「ゆうがた５時　夫婦岩の前で待つ」これでいいか？
This'll do?
Sure, although you write at an
elementary school level...
ああ　平仮名が多すぎるけどな。
あ…だけど俺達
東条の顔　知らねぇんだった。
But we don't know what Tojo looks like.
どうやって渡せばいいんだ？
How should we pass it to him?
In that case...
だったら…おい　邦枝！
Hey, Kunieda!
へ…？
これ。
Here.
《な　なに…？
夕方５時？夫婦岩で待つ…？》
What?
Wait at 5 PM by the two rocks?
Could this be... a confession?
《ってこれ！まさか…告白！？》
Confessing under the sunset sky?
《夕日の中で告白…！？》
（邦枝）《ど　どうしよう　私…
こんな格好で…→
What'll I do?
In this outfit... Maybe I should
have brought a swimsuit after all...
やっぱり　水着
持ってきた方が良かった？》
でも　水着で誘惑して→
But I don't want to be thought of as a woman
who seduces men using sexy swimwear...
男を誘うような女だって
思われたくないし…。
Would you find Tojo and pass this to him?
東条を見つけて
渡してくれねぇか？
Letter of Challenge
うっ…。
He left me with this Letter of Challenge.
（邦枝）
《果たし状　預かっちゃった》
What am I doing?
《私　何やってんだろ…》
はぁ～。
Hey, Kunieda.
（神崎）よお　邦枝。
何　迷ってんだ？
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up, find Tojo, and hand
him that Letter of Challenge.
とっとと東条見つけて
その果たし状　渡してきやがれ。
あんた達の策略には乗らない。
I'm not going to join in on your schemes.
It's too dangerous to let those two fight.
あの２人を戦わせるのは
危険すぎる。
あん？
何言ってんだ？てめえ。
What the hell are you saying?
う…。
じゃ…後は頼んだぞ。
Well, the rest is up to you.
G-Good luck with Tojo.
と　東条によろしくな…。
Is that a Letter of Challenge to Tojo-san?
（相沢）それって
東条さんへの果たし状？
It's almost 5 o'clock.
そろそろ５時だ。
ああ　早くケンカしてえ！
Yeah! I can't wait to fight.
スピー…　スピー…。
Just you wait, Baby Beel!
待ってろよ　ベル坊！もうすぐ
東条に会わせてやっからな！！
We'll meet Tojo soon!
（碇）待ちな　男鹿！
ああ？
Wait, Oga!
ダブ…？アイ…。
誰？
Who are you?
MK5!
ＭＫ５だ！ＭＫ５！！
The MK5!
何の用だよ？急いでんだけど。
What do you want?
I'm in a hurry, you know.
Why don't you join us?
俺達と組まねぇか？
We'll welcome you as our sixth member.
何なら６人目のメンバーとして
迎えてやるぜ？
はぁ？
As the MK6, we'll crush Tojo together!
ＭＫ６として
一緒に東条を倒し→
No one will be able to stop us!
天下取らねぇかって事だよ
ケッヘッへ…。
邪魔！
Out of my way!
（海鳥の鳴き声）
ウ…アウ…。
うわっ！！
ビエエ～ッ！！
ぎゃああ～！
He ain't coming.
（東条）来ねぇ…
チッ…びびったのか？
Is he scared?
It's best if he doesn't show.
《このまま　来なくていい…》
（バイクの音）
ん？
Demons, Catapult, Bremen...
出紋頭　硬破流徒　武頼漢…。
Looks like all the gangs have
joined up to settle things.
この辺りの族が　まとめて
かかってきたんじゃないスか？
Payback for yesterday and today?
昨日　今日の　お礼参り？
Ah, well... Guess I'll
crush them instead of Oga!
しょうがねぇな…男鹿の代わりに
ブチのめしてやるか。
Damn, I'm already really late.
くそっ　すっかり遅れちまった。
ダブ～！
うん？
これは…。
That's...
Tojo's already left.
東条なら帰ったわよ。
You didn't seem like you were coming.
あんたが　なかなか来ないから。
Did Tojo do this?
これは　東条がやったのか？
そう…たった１人でね。
Yes... All by himself.
奴は化け物よ！
He's a monster.
He's not someone you can
beat in a fair fight.
まともに戦って
勝てる相手じゃないわ。
Interesting... Perfect!
おもしれぇ…上等だ。
え？
会うのが
楽しみになってきたぜ！
I can't wait 'till I meet the guy!
ダブ～。
あ～！痛ぇ…。
Oww!
しかし　よく焼けたな…うん？
Well, I did get a nice tan.
ななな…なにぃ～っ！？
What the...
ダ～ッ！ヘヘヘ…！！ダブ～！！
Aloha!
Furuichi here! It's what we've all
been waiting for, summer vacation!
Next week we'll present you with an adventure
love story from a tropical island!
Woohoo!
...wait, what?
This is the municipal pool!
Why?!
On the next Beelzebub:
You're not a bad specimen of a man!
Wait, I can't give up yet!
This time, I'll see Hilda-san in a
swimsuit, and the Queen in a swimsuit...
There might even be a wardrobe malfunction!
If you wanna see that,
take a look at Baby Beel.
He's already lettin' it all hang out.